You
Oh
I
Know too much. They're not going to let us leave
I'm sending for help
Everything is going to be okay. My little Tweety. I promise
Oh
You can jump or we can push you
Someday the truth will be known
You
Oh
Me
Have you gotten into a catapult hoping to be gently and sensibly flown to a destination of your choosing only to be violently
piledrived face burst into the ground
Have you ever set a big stack of TNT on the road hoping to blow up your nemesis?
But when you press the detonator the detonator itself explodes
Have you ever pulled the ripcord of your parachute and only a bunch of silverware comes out?
It's not your fault, there's probably someone to blame
Will be your voice every
Oh
Hey wreck a ball smash, I could probably get you 250 bucks for that. See you next week
Thank you for calling Avery Jones and Maltese if you've been hit by an anvil press one if you've been electrocuted
Press two if you've been crushed by a falling piano press three. Good morning. It's almost three
Good morning, Dottie. Not now. Do they have the paperwork to back it up? Hey, good. You sleeping that suit again? Good. I
I've been waiting for you. Hi. I have found some catastrophic fires
Coincidentally all near matchback. I've been waiting for you. I've been waiting for you. I've been waiting for you
Coincidentally all near match factories and I really think it's a great opportunity to help a lot of people with one case
How long is this internship again?
Through her once just enough time to really dig in and make a difference
You know
You really remind me of when I was fresh out of law school and I mean that in the worst possible way and I will take
That as a compliment. Oh, no, look, you've got this. You know, I'm gonna do you a favor because you're my niece and I want you to
Have a happy life
stop
At Oxford I have a feeling I'm gonna be hearing that phrase a lot at Oxford
They really stress the importance of the law on everyday lives and all you're really having to do right now is brainstorm ideas for your
Billboards. Yeah, you're new here. So you don't know that this file goes right over here
And that my friend is freedom. I really want to pick it up
No, no, and I really want to file it alphabetic. No, you will not please you've got a new client in the conference room
He seems unhinged. Good luck
Oh
Mr. Coyote
Coyote
All right. Well, uh
How can I help you? Oh
One of my billboards
Cost a lot of money to put those up. So you've been in an accident
Do you not talk oh
But you have signs I
Don't understand
All right
That's supposed to be you
Not entirely necessary to do all that but okay
So seems like we're talking about some faulty rocket skates that
Backfired when you're trying to capture a bird that you have some sort of sorted history with
So, do you have the rocket skates?
Okay, great. So we're gonna write in your name as the plaintiff then we'll say we're asking for I don't know three hundred dollars
And here we'll write in the name of the company that made the skates
But they're great to deal with for a little stuff like this we just drop your skates in a box
Type up a complaint and boom you're the richest coyote in the country
All I need is a signature or you just want to lick it. That's probably fine, too
Mr. Coyote somebody grab that guy
Mr. Coyote look I just need you to sign
It's an Acme stapler
Yes, that is how staplers work
Okay, I get it there are problems with Acme's cartoon products I see it all the time
I'm surprised Acme makes my phone in my car. Why would they also make this this is just silly stuff for cartoons
You know, what's the worst that could really happen? They see some birds whipping around their heads
Well doesn't seem that silly to me page this is a run-of-the-mill $300 rocket skate case
Trust me then doesn't that mean that's a pile of $300 cases page?
Come on, you know what would happen if we submitted all this stuff as evidence together
We'd have a giant lawsuit on our hands
And if you could prove a causal connection then really the sky's the limit the sky is not the limit
All right. The limit is like right here. We don't do massive cases. We do quick and easy
So, mr. Coyote my professional opinion is that this case is worth, you know
A few hundred dollars and I can see if they will replace the rocket skates. So we need you to
Rude all right. Well, it was nice meeting you you might put in the evidence box into the system
Oh
Here you go into evidence, please
All right, what do we got here?
Someone's suing for a lot
Oh
Excuse me cartoon products cases go down to the basement
Governor these threats they're tantamount to black man. The law is completely on our side here because we wrote the law
Yeah, okay great to catch up
I
May be straight away on the Plapinger case. Oh, it's done. Let's just say his next vacation will be in prison, but I got something else
Cartoon case basement. Yeah, I think you need to see this one. They're suing us for every acne cartoon product
Who I wasn't familiar with the name
Oh
Look just pay me the money you owe me or I'll sue you for breach of contract. Okay, I gotta go call you later mom
Well, well, well, it isn't our resident hot shot
What does that mean serving acne for every one of their cartoon products?
Yeah, right. Do I look like the guy who would take on the biggest corporation in the world?
You're looking at the guy who is taking on the biggest corporation in the world
Channel 4 news has just learned that papers were filed today against the ACME corporation buddy crane
Acme's chief legal counsel declined to comment
Decline to comment. How did this happen? It's okay. It's okay. It's exciting
All eyes on you ready to show what you got page when we sue Acme for some little thing
Nobody even notices we're a tiny item on a spreadsheet. But this this went to buddy crane
Buddy crane. He's only like the best lawyer in the country. Okay, it's a law school together and he is a total machine
built like an ox his mind as sharp as a tack
trims his
Fingernails with a switch blade, you know, I once saw him eat a lobster
I ate lobster while it was still alive
I'm sure that's legal what can I possibly done to deserve all this that piss off a witch? Oh, no
And I just brought the box inside I've just been working on my short game
I've been on hold for two hours trying to win tickets to the country Jubilee
You
You have any idea what you've done you have put me in such a horrible position
Hi
Yeah, it's been a while
Shake things up. Well, not intentionally shaking really
Your face and my face
Okay, that's looking forward to
From its humble roots as a cartoon anvil factory
Has become America's greatest success story
With each new product we revolutionize industry and the world
We're a company of family values that values its family of companies
acne
I need you to listen to me very carefully. Stop
You're gonna follow my lead
Right. We're gonna tell them this is all just a big misunderstanding and we're looking to get this settled as quickly as possible
We will be polite. We will not detonate explosives
In front of us we will sign it got it
Mr. Avery, you'll pelicanos and mr. Coyote a lot of tickets you buddy
So I hear you guys were friends from back in the day, huh? Guess you could say that if you were incorrect
And look at this guy going clothing optional
Hey buddy, look who's here
Isn't mr. Billboard, how you been man? Yeah, very good. Yeah, those are the days weren't they? Yeah Harvard law you look
Good
Thank you. Have a seat. Okay. I gotta say I was a bit surprised
See your name on a case of this size me too. I mean, yeah, I'm so sorry about all this
Was it just a big misunderstanding? Well, we got a really busy day around here and I would hate to keep you from getting back to
Whenever it is you do. Yeah last stuff too. Yeah. Yeah, sure. Oh
my god
And this seems obvious but I have to say that
Acme denies all charges and accepts no liability or causal connection between mr. Coyote's colorful injuries and our state-of-the-art life-enhancing
Family products. Yeah
And you know much fun as it would be to get back in a courtroom with you
It's time to do what you do best
Settle. Yeah
Well, look, thank you so much. And I'm so sorry for taking up all your time. It was unintentional
Oh
Do you have another copy it's a joke no, no, it's not funny
The cartoons are supposed to be funny. Yes. We want to fight every your tiny farmers have matched
We'll tie you in legal loopholes. We'll bury you in paperwork
I'll put a dozen of my best lawyers in this 24 hours a day to make sure your name is more synonymous with failure
Then it already is
Oh, and I almost forgot we don't validate parking
Do you know what you could do with $50,000? Do you have any idea how many birds you could buy with that?
You know what? Not that it really matters, but I'm out. Yeah, that's right. I quit man
Go find another Laura and this is already my personal freaking nightmare and I'm not sticking around to see if it can get any worse
Oh
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, why didn't you settle?
That's what we do here. We settle dotty. What do we do here? We settle. Okay
I tried to settle but he wouldn't let me settle. He's a coyote. We're not even trial lawyers
I have a miniature golf tournament this weekend
So I don't even know if I'm gonna make it in on Monday plus trial prep adds up photocopies in this economy
But if we beat ACME, then we can afford a ton of photocopies. We won't beat ACME
I mean nobody ever has and nobody ever will the truth is even if you quit right now
The firm is already in the hole for Agnes legal fees and that's just from today. I mean that could close down our doors
look
If we lose we lose if we quit we really lose a lot of money
Okay
Okay, look look we got one true goal for this trial. It's this
We can't look like fools. All right. Our job is not to win this case. Our job is to still be in business when it's over
That's the spirit
Let's talk like lawyers. What a real lawyers do they would find evidence and start making a list of witnesses
The bird he did witness every time an ACME product malfunction he could corroborate Wiley's story
Sure, whatever add the Roadrunner to our witness list one more thing. Um, where is mr. Coyote gonna stay?
Oh
All right, don't give me that look yeah, I live in a motel look I got pool access, you know
There's no mortgage never have to make my bed
There's an incredible all-you-can-eat seafood buffet around the corner at tissues come out of a bathroom wall
Hi Jerry, yeah
One one second
Yeah, hi I need another room for a few nights not near me
Please
He's not a pet he looks like a pet
Who rents a separate room for their pets cherry? Come on. I've been living here for almost five years. You know me no
pets
Okay, you want to do this legally speaking a pet is a domesticated or tamed animal kept as a companion in or outside an
Individual's residence. This is mr. Coyote. He is my client
He's not my pet nor anyone's pet in the eyes of the law and as such that sign or any rule that accompanies it does
Not apply to him. All right, it does not say no animals and just my unbiased opinion
He may actually have a case against you for discrimination
Yeah
He pees on the rug it's on you all right deal but I would need a full workup of urine analysis
It's a motel plenty of people pee on the rug
Right next door
I
Think up next a mouse breaks the sound barrier
Know
You're kind of a psychopath aren't you
Oh
Watch and learn so we take the subpoena like so just cover it with copious amounts of birdseed
Roadrunner eats the bird seed grabs a subpoena and boom. He's legally obligated to show up to court
instant Roadrunner trap
Beep beep this is a kind of inside thing with you guys
Is
Everyone clear on our plan
Page what's our plan?
So we have to prove to jury that acne cartoon products are at fault for every accident that Wiley's had going back here
So we are going to take pictures and we're gonna gather evidence and we're gonna put the evidence in little bags
And we're gonna interview experts and witnesses and we're going to highlight big books of photocopy
Documents and we're gonna pound the pavement and we're gonna study up
I'm gonna try and catch our big eyewitness by leaving a nice note in the desert
And if we follow my plan by the end of this, we'll have enough evidence to take acne down
We really have nothing I mean I kind of assumed that we'd have nothing but this is nothing
All right
The court of the Second Judicial Circuit of Albuquerque is now in session
The honorable judge drop a grosso presiding
May be seated
Human human
Carto
Quiet
My name is judge
Trap a grosso name of the case is coyote versus acne. I am NOT a loosey goosey judge
I am a no-nonsense. No silly stuff judge. Is that understood?
Mr. Crane
Oh
We live in a great country don't we because it's one that values freedom above all else
You're free to live your life any way you see fit could mean living in the desert
Out in the cave spending your days chasing after a bird who is much much faster than you
But that that is your right
as an American
But that freedom it comes with great responsibility if you're gonna take a missile for instance, and you're gonna glue handlebars to it
Well, that's that's your choice
But we expect you to understand at that missile in those handlebars. They aren't designed to catch birds
What I will prove to this jury
Is that man?
Wiley coyote he
Is reckless and all of his injuries are self-inflicted. I
Mean we won't condemn him you or I we all know who's responsible
It's clear as the desert sky. I think I just laid an egg. God bless America. God bless the troops
Damn that was really good. Oh
Please don't write that down
And and please don't write that down or that down
Mr. Avery
I
Know
Now what what did the defense say we're gonna argue?
Huh?
I mean, I know the answer to it. I know the answer. I'm not asking you a question
I mean it is it is a question, but it's a question that I'm asking to me. Let me start over. Let me start over
objection to my start
So the defense said that we were gonna argue that
The products are dangerous and that acne is negligent in selling them. I do really agree with all that
Yeah, I mean, it's not fancy, but it's true
I'm sorry one second, please
We don't need evidence right now, mr. Avery, okay
Excuse me, your honor. My client would like me to show you this defective acme rocket scape
And as you can see there's a faulty on switch
Nothing
God bless America
Bless the troops
Opening arguments today in Coyote v. Acme sources close to the case report that Acme is doing a
Fantastic job protecting their brand and dignity while the plaintiff appears hungry and afraid more after this
Yeah
Noise complaints about a loud TV. Seriously, it's the TV you're having a problem with. Okay
Cherry I turned it off
You sure you have the right number
Oh my god, you could stop this case
Where do I find
Doesn't sound like a place I want to go
Will I be able to contact you again
Oh
Buddy I say buddy you little rascal you I was more more the tax havens so nice. They named it twice
So I say I heard we have ourselves a lawsuit in the animated sector
Talks PR about this, you know, it's a local paper and pretty flattering
You know, I'm a witness case as fast as I can
But in the meantime think things like this make us look pretty good in the public eye not ideal
But you know, it's like killing two birds with
One stone two birds one stone what a vile
expression I only rotten
We both know it would be very I say very unpleasant for everyone involved if anything bigger
I say bigger were to become public
Oh
Mysterious college, it's so cool. So what do you sound like? I don't know. He's kind of like hey, what's up doc?
I have information chomp chomp chomp. It was like chewing on a cracker or something. Okay
Well map is saying it should be right here
It's just a wall
Jack there Jack anywhere
Wait, what's that? Oh that kind of Jack somebody's got a sense of humor
Well, there's a duck and he is sitting feels a bit easy well good thing I like easy
Excuse me
Hi, uh, my name is Kevin Avery. This is Paige. I'm a personal injury attorney. Well, look who decided to show up
Oh great. Thank you. I wasn't sure if you knew we were coming
You're a little late and you're still wearing that hideous suit. Take your pants off right over there, please and
strike a pose
No, it's so difficult to find nude models these days sit down
We're all right. Thank you disrobe and pretend you're thinking I expect this is going to take a few hours
Yeah, um, we had an anonymous caller say that you might have some important information
Yeah information that can help us enter a case quickly information
Yes
About acne
Oh, yes
Oh, he really shouldn't be here
Hello
Oh
Well, we drove him crazy and we got a can of page well could be important clearly he's been holding on to this for a while
Wait
That's all folks
Are we the folks
Do you think we're gonna get kidnapped held for ransom I feel so alive
So, what do you think it is
Thanks
Oh
That looks unspeakably dangerous and yet he walked in anyway
What are you doing I'm following Wiley I
Just look like a loser if I stay out here
I
Come into the tunnel
Hello
But they don't tell you to walk down mysterious tunnels in your fancy classes at Oxford
But they discourage it actually actually I thought about majoring in mysterious tunnels
No, you did. Yeah, I did
We got here
Hey, I found a message
It says Daffy I'm not sure how long I have I hope this message gets to you
Oh
Things have gone awry with project
Sisyphus
What is project Sisyphus?
Acne is watching my every move and I have a feeling I'm in grave danger
If you see this message, please send help dr. Laurie
Oh
Did I not say unspeakably dangerous
Didn't I say those exact words
Okay, so Sisyphus is some Greek mythology and he was punished by the gods and made to roll a boulder up a hill
Every day, but it would just roll right back down for eternity
And it was also at Daffy was painting
So what that's not evidence. None of this is gonna help us win a trial
All right, this is it's all just a waste of our time
We have a client who no offense can't read a warning label
We have piles and piles of stuff that he himself broke
We have nothing Paige
You've been settling Acme cases for years and you have never stopped to think and see a pattern a pattern
Yes, my clients go boom and two seconds later. They're fine. Nobody cares
So that makes it okay boom
$100 that's fair
This case can make it right. This is your opportunity to really show people what you're capable of
Yeah, but that only works if I don't lose and why do you assume you're gonna lose are you kidding
It is really super easy to lose
It was better you learn that now
You know everyone thought I was crazy for coming here
But I didn't want to just go to some big law firm and help the rich guys get richer
I thought
I thought you were actually still a real lawyer
Yeah, me too
You
So
What is it about the roadrunner
I
There are no words
What I I envy you really it must be nice to have such a such a clear goal
I mean I used to have that I think
I was hungry and I was chasing but I didn't like the pressure of having to always win
It got burnt out on trying
Anyway, you're a really good listener
We were having a heart to heart
So
You made it well you go a long way to make a point
Hey wiley, thanks. I'll see you tomorrow
So
Are you sitting down, uh, yes, well sales not is that gonna be a problem
Wiley is conning us. The only reason he's doing this case is to catch and kill the roadrunner during the trial
That's not good
It's all just part of a plot
It's just using us so we'll put the bird on the witness stand if the roadrunner shows up to court
It'll be chaos. I'll look like a fool if the firm will fold. We'll be mattress salesmen
That's kind of demeaning to mattress salesmen fine. We'll be uh garbage men kevin
Okay garbage people my dad's garbage people
Okay, i'm just really nervous about letting wiley back into this courtroom without wiley. There's no trial with no trial
There's no firm and without the firm we're gonna be broke
I hate to suggest lying to a dog, but you're gonna have to convince him that the roadrunner will be there
Pete I was wrong see what you can find out about project sisyphus and how it's connected to acme great i'm already on it
Okay
So
Hi, I was just wondering if a dr. Laurie still lives here
Hey listen, you know, would you like some tea, dearie?
I'm tickled. It was a very happy marriage. He used to work long days
But would still come home and play the piano for me for hours because he knew how much I loved it
We had 87 years together. I am grateful
Um, when did dr. Laurie pass away if you don't mind me asking? Oh, he's not dead
He's missing
He went to work one day with our little bird and I never saw either of them again
They told me he ran off with his secretary, but I don't think so. His secretary was a penguin
What can you tell me about project sisyphus?
So
What
Which day what?
Oh, which day is the roadrunner testifying?
Any day now why do you have any particular reason for wanting to catch up with him?
Okay, well i'll keep you posted
I
Need this roadrunner
Absolutely. Why exactly?
He's the only one that's seen every time this moron's used our products incorrect. I bet he's holding a grudge
Go out there and you bring him to me. How hard could it be to catch a bird?
Do
Liar
Nobody's seen
Who is the Paywall?
Hello
My husband was the head inventor of animated products at Acne.
He was so excited when he got the job.
He wanted to make things that really helped cartoons.
Like the anti-lump pump.
An eraser of stinky lines.
Oh, and this anti-predator spray.
After a while, things changed.
He didn't like what was going on.
And then, he disappeared.
Recently, I've been getting phone calls.
Sometimes they hang up.
But sometimes...
I don't know the man on the telephone.
I don't know where my dear husband went.
But I know Project Sisyphus is the reason he's gone.
Target acquired. Commence project roadkill in T-minus three, two, one.
Sir, the target is looking at us.
Why is the target looking at us?
We tweaked! We tweaked!
Did we catch him?
Oh, my head is on fire!
Fire!
So, obviously, we hit a speed bump.
Does it itch? Yes.
But I'm afraid to touch it.
You, eyes and ears out there, what happened?
What did you see?
Well, I thought I'd talk.
You thought you'd talk?
I don't pay you to tink you talk. I pay you to talk.
I talk!
You talk or you taught you talk?
Because you just said you taught you talk.
I did. I did talk.
What did you teach? What did you talk?
A breakdown on the eastern perimeter.
Ultimately, that's where he ran off.
That roadrunner is very, very fast, sir.
Step your game up, bird. They're getting too close.
I don't just want them scared. I want them ruined.
I want them to stop digging around.
You know what happened to Dr. Laurie.
You want the same thing to happen to your granny.
No, please! I'll get him tonight.
I promise.
Hey, great job, big dog.
Shut up, Patches!
Absolutely, sir. I won't say another word.
I wish I could say more,
but Acme has ears and eyes and ears everywhere.
But Acme has ears and eyes and ears everywhere.
Paige? Are you okay?
Oh, I'm totally fine.
I've always kind of wanted to throw a bomb out of a window,
but there just never really was the right time.
Listen, Dr. Laurie's widow gave me this tape,
and I've listened to it a thousand times,
and there's something in the background.
But Acme has ears and eyes and ears everywhere.
That's the guy who called me.
Yeah, I know, but can you hear it?
I wish I could say more,
but Acme has ears and eyes and ears everywhere.
Wait, Wiley! That's evident!
Okay, that's enough.
Wiley, stop that.
Is there some kind of plan to this?
There it is.
Wait, I know this song.
From where?
I don't know.
It's like a TV show or an ad or...
Wait.
Albuquerque's annual carrot festival.
Okay, what is that?
A festival of carrots in Albuquerque.
It happens every year annually.
Hello?
Mystery caller?
Mystery caller, who called me?
Tell him we're from Avery Jones and Maltese.
We're from Avery Jones and Maltese.
You can show yourself at any time.
So, uh, what is up, Doc?
Who's there?
I'll never tell you, Mac.
I'm a creature than I am, a shadow that moves.
You'll never figure out who I am.
Oh, my. Oh, heavens.
You've seen my face. Don't look at me.
I'm too... beautiful.
Mystery caller?
I tell you, the budgie has been bumbling
and stumbling your way through this case for weeks.
You're lucky you have me on your side.
Hey, you been followed? Got eyes on you?
Caught by a red light camera? Spotted by a drone?
Have you been bugged?
This is just getting embarrassing now.
Look, I got, like, a million questions for you.
Why didn't you call again?
What happened to Dr. Laurie?
And what can you tell us about project systems?
Enough with the questions, counselor.
This calls for a flashback.
Dr. Laurie was the head inventor
of Acme cartoon products, you see.
He built some amazing things.
Essentials, like the good change machine.
One day, they sent an executive from corporate
to oversee things.
Guy was a real toy.
Suddenly, there was a lot of secrets.
They called it Project Sisyphus.
Under the new management,
the test became increasingly reckless.
I'm not sure I understand.
What was it all for?
They weren't inventing products for cartoons.
They were using cartoons to invent products.
Dr. Laurie told them this was wrong
and that the tests were harmful to cartoons.
He pleaded with them to put an end to it.
But instead, they put an end to him.
Everyone who worked on Project Sisyphus
is either missing,
or forced to work for Acme,
or quacked.
And when did the program end?
Don't you see?
It never ended.
It evolved.
Instead of testing dangerous products in the lab,
they let them out into the real world.
Yes.
Wiley's rocket skates.
They were designed to backfire.
Now you're getting it.
The more something breaks,
the more a cartoon gets hurt,
the more data to make better Acme products for humans.
Exactly, exactly.
Wiley, you're what they call a high usage user.
They let you boom and splat and bang
for years and years,
knowing full well the toll.
Would you testify to this in court?
The world needs to hear this.
No, no, no.
You need someone on the inside to spill the beans.
Get the head of PR at Acme to testify.
He's a master of spin.
His name is...
Uh-oh.
That's my cue.
I think they got him.
They didn't.
Hey, if anyone asks,
tell them you're informed it was a little hunter with a funny hat.
We're all counting on you.
Bye.
Yeah, that's great.
No one's gonna get through that door.
Any added security is great.
Will you tell us your role at Acme for the record?
Okay, great.
If he says anything wrong, we'll get him out of here.
Done.
And what does your role as PR representative entail?
Acme.
So you have authority to speak for Acme.
What can you tell us about Project Sisyphus?
Mr. Devil, what is Project Sisyphus?
May I remind you, you are under oath.
Put it...
Objection?
Counselors, approach the bench.
This case is turning my courtroom into a circus.
They just ejected my witness.
We don't know that.
Couldn't agree more, Your Honor.
I'd like to file a motion to exclude all evidence
submitted by the prosecution.
Say the original pair of rocketskates.
All else is overreaching.
Motion granted.
Are you kidding?
Thank you, Your Honor.
Now in response, I'd like to file a motion for dismissal
due to lack of evidence.
Motion granted.
I'm tired of all this bunk.
You're not allowed to say that.
That's the beauty of being a judge.
I can say whatever I want.
Miss trial, there, I said it.
Case dismissed.
I have a comment.
What happened in there was a miscarriage of justice,
but it was not a surprise.
The Acme Corporation has knowingly
been putting dangerous products
into the hands of cartoons for decades.
Acme has gone to great lengths
to cover up an insidious plot
that they call Project Sisyphus.
They have threatened the safety of myself and my client.
Look, bombs, boulders, pianos,
they will stop at nothing.
But myself and my associates,
we will keep fighting.
I mean, these companies think they can do
whatever they want and get away with all of it.
Because they do.
We're sick of it.
And it stops now.
So we're getting ready to launch a...
Excuse me.
Moment. Excuse me.
Wally!
More chaos in court today after the Acme trial
was dismissed by the very fair
and honorable Judge Tropogrosso.
The plaintiffs made their objections known
by wrestling a six-foot cartoon rocket.
It's all good.
Nothing to see here.
Is that your car?
Hey, Paige.
Have you seen?
What?
Your speech.
It's the number one trending news item
in the country right now.
It's everywhere.
What?
Do you like Miss Paige?
Well, and the car exploding,
I think, is a part of it.
Mr. Avery!
How you gonna go?
Any comment?
No comment.
Mr. Avery!
Any comment on Congress
agreeing to hear your case?
Uh, uh, Congress?
Thoughts on Foghorn Lykorn
agreeing to testify.
No, did you say Congress?
They're putting Acme under the microscope.
You're going to D.C.
We're going to D.C.?
Uh, okay, well, uh,
no, no comment.
Mr. Avery!
Wait.
Where are you going?
What?
Wiley, no.
You can't go.
I need you in D.C.
I mean, this is the big showdown.
If you don't show up,
there's no hearing.
This whole thing will have been for nothing.
The rubber runner will be there.
Yeah, of course.
He'll be there.
Yeah, he's coming.
I promise.
So, come on.
What do you say?
The whole world will be what?
And he'll be there.
All right.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Mr. Avery!
Mr. Avery, how's the water?
What initially seemed to be a case of routine product malfunction
has turned into a David versus Goliath tale as old as time.
Would like to wish our furry little friend good luck in D.C.
We're rooting for you, Wiley,
and we always were from day one.
When a company is this successful,
there's always someone looking to tear it down,
but our hands are clean.
Five attendants prepare for landing.
Sorry about that initial wrong turn out of Albuquerque, folks.
This is it.
No more warnings.
I don't care if you kidnap him, run him out of town,
or throw him down a hole.
Wiley Coyote will not be at the hearing tomorrow.
Are we clear?
Yes, boss.
We'll clear.
Please be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Wiley, please be quiet.
Look, I promise you what I have to do
is more important than what you have to do.
There's been a change of plans.
Look, he...
he couldn't make it, right?
He made it.
Okay, fine.
You think I would drag the Road Runner out here
so you could destroy me in front of the entire world?
Yeah, I know you just wanted him in that courtroom
so you could catch him and eat him.
Why would I help you do that?
Okay, yeah.
I lied.
I needed you to stay with this case.
Huh? You misled me.
You made me think that this case was about something.
And it is!
You know, this is way bigger than the Road Runner.
Did you not even process what the rabbit said?
You're a high-usage user.
I mean, look at all this stuff.
You're addicted.
Every explosion, every time you fell
to the bottom of a canyon, Acme wanted that.
You know, I changed around my whole life for you.
My entire routine.
You're probably all gonna blow up in my face
because you wanted a drumstick.
Oh, myself?
You have only cared about your plan this entire time.
Oh, the Road Runner, the Road Runner.
I'm so sick of this Road Runner.
You're never gonna catch him!
Okay?
You just... You really aren't.
Just stop trying.
Yeah?
Hey, Kev. Look, I didn't want to have to tell you
this right before the hearing, but, uh...
we've spent every last cent on this trial.
We're out of money.
So, what does that mean?
It means unless there's some kind of miracle,
there's not gonna be a firm to come back to.
I made you guys appointments to donate plasma next week.
I can't go.
I don't want to put this kind of pressure on you,
we just thought you should know.
Okay.
Damn it.
She's here.
Ela.
You missed.
Well done, efficiency-wise.
Lucky.
Uh, I'm trying to become more...
You look weird.
You missed!
Wiley! Wiley!
Oh boy.
Wiley!
Grab my hand! I'm trying to save you!
Stop!
Look, Wiley, I'm sorry! I made a mistake!
Wait! Wait, Wiley!
Oh no! Oh no! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Uh, what is to hold up?
He's in the bathroom.
Take care of him.
It's like you had a rough night, huh?
Oh, thanks for your believable concern.
Come on, do you really want to go out there?
I mean, with those cameras?
The pressure?
What is it?
I don't know.
What is this?
It's everything you ever wanted. Freedom from responsibility.
It's no strings attached. That is under the table. It's for you.
All I gotta do is walk out the store right now.
I mean, come on. I really want to just keep doing the same thing over and over again.
Try, fail, try, fail. Expecting a different result.
I just realized that, uh, yeah, I do.
I do.
You get the gist.
Oh my god, you look like a stuntman.
Is Wiley here?
He's not with you?
I haven't seen him since we were going 80 miles an hour on the highway strapped to a refrigerator.
What the hell? I thought you guys were in the hotel room next to me. I feel so left out.
I really screwed up. He knows the rotator's not coming. He knows I lied.
Oh, my jerk. I should have been honest with him. It just seemed easier.
Mr. Avery, thank you for joining us today.
We are here to determine whether or not Acme products are a danger to society.
Where is your client?
I'm, uh, not entirely sure, to be honest.
Senator Fudd, the fact that Mr. Coyote hasn't deemed it necessary to grace us with his presence at the scheduled time
should tell you all you need to know about his character.
I think this does tell us a lot.
Look, my client has a long history with Acme.
He's been using their products, sorry, products for decades.
Why is that? If they're so... dangerous.
Well, he doesn't have a choice, really.
Acme has a monopoly over all the tools required for Mr. Coyote's work.
His work? I have hear that he's unemployed and living in a cave.
Truth, truth. It's a fact.
No, no, no, no.
Pursuant to Sylvester V. Gonzalez, chased by Predator is a legal occupation under the law.
He may not get a salary, but he works.
In fact, he's one of the most hard-working people I've ever met.
And he's brave.
He will walk out onto the tiniest rope over the largest canyon.
He'll straddle a rocket that he's glued handlebars to without batting an eye.
I mean...
Sorry.
Look, when Mr. Coyote first walked into my office,
I was the laziest person you could ever imagine.
I didn't want to work. I didn't want to try anything.
Because deep down, I didn't want to fail.
But he's not afraid of that.
No matter what happens, he picks himself up.
He tries again and again and again and again.
He would never think of quitting.
He wakes up every morning with purpose and with hope.
And I think everyone should be inspired by that.
I know I am.
You don't need signs anymore.
Thank you for telling me that.
Mr. Weghorn, thank you for taking the time for a mere busy schedule.
Now we've requested that Mr. Avery asks you a few questions today.
I've been studying this guy for a long time.
He's a genius.
I've been studying this guy in interviews.
He's a blowhard. He's a huge ego.
Here I am, son.
All right, I can work with him.
I can work with him.
Mr. Weghorn, are you aware of the ACME program known as Project Sisyphus?
I am familiar with the name.
Okay, and how would you explain the type of program that it is to this committee?
Why, it's one of research and development.
Great, so you're constantly innovating your cartoon product line to make it better.
Yes, sir.
Okay, that makes sense.
But if you're studying these products so closely, why are they malfunctioning so frequently?
That sounds like something you might tinker with.
Well, son, business is complex.
Okay, now does any of the information that you get from Project Sisyphus go into developing the human line?
Sure, sure.
Okay, so you admit it.
He just admitted it. Did you hear that?
He admitted it.
You're intentionally giving dangerous products to cartoons, willfully causing pain to millions in this process.
Do you think progress isn't worth a little pain, a little discomfort?
It is, son, it always has been.
Besides, nothing we've done today or any other day is illegal.
Isn't that right, Mr. Cray?
Absolutely, absolutely.
The law is completely on our side here and so is the popular opinion.
Thank you, Mr. Cray.
Mr. Langhorne.
And another thing.
Take a seat, son.
I'm asking the questions here.
There's nothing cuter than this, prosecutor.
I am reminded of my days as a little rooster.
I am reminded of my days as a little rooster on the poultry farm where I learned a valuable lesson.
Cartoons are resilient.
Hit us with a mallet, throw us off a cliff.
We can take it.
Speaking as a cartoon, I think it can even be a little bit funny.
Am I right?
So what's a little pain for the greater good?
Pain is a part of life and it's valuable.
You like that comfortable rubber in those shoes there, don't you, son?
Well, that's duty-free.
We developed it by bouncing it one million times off the face of a cartoon.
Those tornado pills became jet propellers.
That high-speed tonic got us to the moon.
So, yes, yes, our cartoon products sometimes do explode.
Sometimes they do backfire.
Sometimes they push the boundaries of gravity and science.
But do you all want to live in a world without new, without progress?
Now, what is it you always say, Mr. Crane?
You can't make an omelet without breaking a few eggs.
Well, that's right.
And in this case, if that egg is some lowlife, cave-bwelling desert dog with no connections, no family, no friends, I'm sorry, but so be it.
No harm, no foul.
That is not an accurate depiction of my client.
Well, I was under the impression that no one would speak on his behalf apart from his lawyer.
Is there anyone in the whole wide world who cares what happens to the coyote at all?
Mr. Runner, we will be asking you a series of yes or no questions.
Two beeps for yes, one beep for no.
Do you understand?
Beep, beep.
Are you a bird?
Are you easy to catch?
Beep.
Okay, good.
Are you familiar with a Mr. Wile E. Coyote?
Beep, beep.
Have you witnessed Mr. Coyote using any acne products while in your presence in the desert?
Have those products always failed?
Beep, beep.
Mr. Runner, have you been a witness to Mr. Coyote's pain and suffering?
Yeah, me too.
Would you call him a friend?
Beep, beep.
Well, thank you, Mr. Runner, thank you for coming here today.
Did you have something additional you'd like to say?
Beep, beep.
All right, the floor is yours to add to the record.
The floor is yours to add to the record.
Are you coming back?
Mr. Avery, I must admit, I am very, very moved.
However, you have offered no proof of Acme's culpability
other than the pain and suffering of this one singular coyote.
Therefore, as much as it pains me,
you leave me no other choice.
I will not allow you to do so.
Therefore, as much as it pains me,
you leave me no other choice.
All in agreement to dismiss this investigation say aye.
Aye.
Try, fail.
Well, no hard feelings, boys.
It's a tough world out there.
Better luck next time.
I think those are the birds you're looking for.
Go for it.
Proposterous, I say, preposterous.
Watch your tongue.
Get me out of here.
I want justice.
If anyone is live streaming, I will be live suing.
Do you understand?
I have a medical condition.
I'm medically more important than all of you.
Okay, seriously, guys, no pictures.
Get back here, Avery.
You can't walk away from me in a suit like that.
Do you know how much I'm worth?
Don't you laugh, son.
I don't pay you to laugh.
Well, we tried.
We tried.
And thank you both for pushing me.
Wait.
What's going on?
Hey, look!
It's the lawyers!
The lawyers!
They're here!
Thank you for what you've done.
What is this?
They all want to sue Acme.
Even after how poorly you did.
They trust you.
Avery Jones and Maltese.
Hey!
Can you believe that?
Oh, something's in your office.
Apparently, it's very important.
We got it.
Hey, counselor. You put up a good fight at congress.
But nothing says guilty
better than some cold, hard evidence.
Here's a gift from yours truly
from inside the doors at Acme.
What's this?
About five years worth of cases.
Looks like we got our work cut out for us.
Shocking new developments
in the unfolding Acme case today.
Newly leaked footage from
Project Sisyphus triggered a
pre-dawn raid on company headquarters
that quickly led to the arrest
of Buddy Crane, Acme's chief
legal counsel and CEO
Foghorn Leghorn, for their
participation in the alleged misconduct.
I'm a cage-free rooster!
Also at the scene, investigators
rescued Dr. Peter Lorry,
an Acme scientist who went missing
over 30 years ago.
His upcoming testimony regarding
Project Sisyphus promises to bring
the truth to light.
Oh, dearie!
Don't be a stranger.
What's this?
About five years worth of cases.
Shocking new developments
in the unfolding Acme case today.
Newly leaked footage from
Project Sisyphus triggered a
pre-dawn raid on company headquarters
that quickly led to the arrest
of Buddy Crane, Acme's chief
legal counsel and CEO
Foghorn Leghorn, for their
participation in the alleged misconduct.
I'm a cage-free rooster!
Also at the scene, investigators
...
Well, sky's the limit.
Sky's the limit.
Breaking rocks in a hot sun.
I fought for law and
the law won.
I needed money, God, I had none.
I fought for law and
the law won.
I left my baby and it feels so bad.
I guess my race is run.
She's the best girl
that I ever had.
I fought for law and
the law won.
I left my baby and it feels so bad.
I guess my race is run.
She's the best girl that I ever had.
I fought for law and
the law won.
I lost my gold and
I lost my phone.
I fought for law and
the law won.
I left my baby and it feels so bad, I guess my race is run
She's the best girl I've ever had
I fought the Lord and the Lord won, I fought the Lord and the
I fought the Lord and the Lord won I fought the Lord and ah, the law won
I fought the law and I'll lower it.
Thank you.